<?xml version="1.0"?>
<hspage>
    <title>How to archive your music collection to CD</title>
    <menu name="mghelp" selected="How To"/>
	<pagecontent>
        <p class="longtext">
            It is assumed here that you have a part of your collection already recorded to CD, and that a part of the songs you have on CD is also on your hard drive (because yes, you <b>do</b> listen to the music you have!). What you want to do is to record a new set of CDs, that would be organized in a <b>CD A-Z</b> format (Example: CD A-C, CD C-F... CD R-Z), and would include both your already recorded songs and the songs you have on your hard drive. It is also assumed that you want the structure of your songs on your CDs to be <b>Artist/Album/Track - Artist - Title</b>.
        </p>
        <ol>
            <li><a href="build_music_collection.htm">Build your collection</a> and don't forget to add your CDs to it!</li>
            <li>Click on <b>Design Board</b>.</li>
            <li>Click on the checkbox next to you hard drive location in the <b>Locations pane</b>.</li>
            <li>Click on the checkbox next to each of your CD locations.</li>
            <li>In the menu, click on <b>Design|Mass Rename</b>.</li>
            <li>Click on <b>OK</b>.</li>
            <li>Click on <b>Menu|Design|Move Conflicts</b>.</li>
            <li>Make sure that no song from your hard drive location (Look at the <b>Location</b> column) has been sent to the ignore box. This shouldn't happen because you added your hard drive location <b>before</b> your CD locations.</li>
            <li>There might be some inconsistencies in the <b>Mass Rename</b> result due to inconsistent tags. You can merge directories together by dragging a directory's content in another directory.</li>
            <li>Click on <b>Split into CD/DVD</b>.</li>
            <li>Select <b>CD &lt;First Letter&gt; - &lt;Last Letter&gt;</b></li>
            <li>If you really want to record as few CD as possible, leave the <b>Grouping level</b> slider at the extreme left. But if you want to prevent your artists from being splitted, put the slider on the second tick.</li>
            <li>Click on <b>OK</b></li>
            <li>Click on <b>Materialize</b>.</li>
            <li>Select <b>Record renamed songs to CD/DVD</b>.</li>
            <li>Click on <b>Next</b>.</li>
            <li>Review your to-be-recorded CDs and recording options and click on <b>Next</b>.</li>
            <li>If you think you can free enough space to go at the recommended free space level, it would be a good idea to do it now. Having the recommended free space prevent musicGuru from asking more than once for a CD to fetch songs from. If you don't have a screen about free disk space, it is because you don't have any CD on your design board, and you don't need to worry about this. Click on <b>Next</b>.</li>
            <li>From now on, musicGuru will prompt you, either for a blank CD or a CD from your collection (so it can fetch songs from it). Just follow the instructions until you get a screen telling you that you are finished.</li>
            <li>Click on <b>Finish</b>.</li>
        </ol>
	</pagecontent>
</hspage>