<?xml version="1.0"?>
<hspage>
    <title>How to resolve name conflicts</title>
    <menu name="mghelp" selected="How To"/>
	<pagecontent>
        <p class="longtext">
            When playing around with your design board, it might happen that 2 or more files fight for the same name, in the same directory. When this happens, these files are considered conflictual, and all files with the same name, except the first that was placed there, are given a conflict prefix ([000], [001], etc.). There are a few useful things you should know about conflicts.
        </p>
        <sub title="Look at the location column">
            The design board and the ignore box both have a <b>Location</b> column. This column is very useful to know which conflict goes where. For a song, that column displays the location that song is from. For a directory, that column displays a list of locations that are the source of <b>all files in the directory</b>. So if, for example, you just clicked on <b>Move Conflicts</b> and you want to be sure that no files from your main collection didn't go in the ignore box, just look at the <b>Location</b> column next to the <b>conflicts</b> directory created, and verify that your collection is not in the list.
        </sub>
        <sub title="The order in which you add your location to the design board is important">
            The order in which you add your location to the design board determines, in a <b>Mass Rename</b>, which files will be conflictual. So if, for example, you first add your hard drive location, and then your CD locations to the design board, only songs from your CD locations can be conflictual, unless, of course, you have 2 songs in your hard drive collection conflicting together. 
        </sub>
        <sub title="Moving your conflicts">
            The quickest way to move your conflicts is to use the <b>Move Conflicts</b> feature. It takes all conflicts and move them to the ignore box, in a directory called <b>conflicts</b>. You can also manually move them around with drag and drop. Renaming a file is also one way to resolve a conflict.
        </sub>
	</pagecontent>
</hspage>